坏  种
早餐就要好了 小甜熊
Breakfast in five, honey bear.
好的 爸爸
Ok, daddy.
我尝一点
I'm gonna steal one of these.
要多点鸡蛋吗
Want some more eggs?
不了 谢谢
No thanks.
埃利斯老师给我们看了今年的奖项
Miss Ellis showed us this years Citizenship Award.
是块金牌
It's a medal.
特别大
It's really big.
像奥运金牌那样
Like the Olympics.
真的吗
Really?
呃 也没那么大
Well, not that big.
但是也很大了
But it's pretty big.
我会拿下它的
I'm gonna win it.
我觉得你肯定会赢得它的
It wouldn't surprise me a bit if you did.
金牌颁给有圣奥尔登价值观的人
It's given to the person who exemplifies St. Alden's values.
信仰 诚实 修养 怜悯
Faith, honesty, grace, and compassion.
如果你没赢得金牌
I just don't want you to be disappointed
你也不用沮丧
if you don't win it.
你什么时候再去约会
When are you having another date?
怎么了
Why?
你很在意这事吗
Does it bother you when I date?
没有 我怎么会在意呢
No, why would it bother me?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 安琪拉姑姑
Hey, Aunt Angela.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 小甜熊
Hey, honey bear.
我给你找了个妹子
I found your gal.
艾玛正和我聊我约会的事呢
Em and I were just talking about me dating.
不是约会 是找到新保姆了
Not a date, I found you a nanny.
那不是我的任务吗
Wasn't that the assignment?
我是说 新保姆
I- I mean, new babysitter.
我知道你不需要新保姆
I know you don't need a new nanny.
我也不需要临时保姆
I don't need a new babysitter, either.
太逊了
It's stupid.
她还在为莱薇娅难过
She's still upset about Miss Levia.
你应该照顾我 安琪拉姑姑
You should babysit me, Aunt Angela.
那是我的荣幸 我的女王
It would be an honour, my queen,
但我的病人可能会反对
but I think my patients might object.
别担心 艾玛
Don't worry, Em.
我会找一个你喜欢的保姆
I'm gonna find you someone you like.
哦 她还说这个学期会再拿个金牌
Oh, she also says she's gonna win another award this semester.
哦
Oh.
她真有干劲啊
She's got drive.
你该很兴奋吧
You should be thrilled.
是吗 艾玛
Right, Emma?
艾玛
Emma?
外面喷水池里有只死猫
There's a dead cat in the fountain.
别伤心
Don't be sad.
可能事发迅疾
It probably happened very fast.
我觉得它不会感到痛苦
I don't think it felt a thing.
啊 啊啊啊
Ah! Ahhh!!!
冷静 各位
Calm down, everyone.
我保证 它更加害怕你
I guarantee you it's more afraid of you than you are of it.
艾玛·格罗斯曼
Emma Grossman!
谢谢你 艾玛
Thank you, Emma.
不客气 埃利斯老师
You're welcome, Mrs. Ellis.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我们家后院有个蜂窝
We have a nest in our back yard.
我爸爸说黄蜂只有受到威胁才会攻击
My dad says wasps only attack when they feel threatened.
这是它们的本能 麦洛
It's nature, Milo.
但愿你不会对尘土过敏
I hope you're not allergic to dust.
这里可能不是开会的好地方
This probably isn't the best place in the house
但是 我们开会的时间不多
to have a meeting but I'm on a deadline.
没事
No worries.
你什么工作都在这里做吗
Do you make everything here?
不 几乎都不会来这里
No, hardly anything anymore.
我有两个工厂 这里是刚刚创业的地方
I have two factories going but this is where it all began.
厉害
Cool.
那说说你吧
So tell me about you.
简历上说你是职业滑雪运动员
Your resume says you were a professional snowboarder.
对 直到我交叉韧带断了
Yep, right up until I blew out my ACL.
我不希望听到这个
I hate to hear that.
那样最好
It's for the best.
我深受打击 于是就试着做些安稳的工作
I still hit it hard, I just try to avoid the dangerous stuff.
也对
Sure.
那你做保姆有五年了
So you've been a nanny for five years?
是的
That's right.
看起来你挺喜欢这样
You seem to like it.
我喜欢孩子
I love kids.
没有别的 他们都很单纯
There's no BS. They're not complicated.
如果他们伤心了 就会哭
If they're sad, they cry.
倘若他们开心了 就会笑
If they're happy, they laugh.
惹人喜欢
It's refreshing.
那还有别的事我需要了解的吗
So is there anything else I need to know?
你的推荐人好像都很喜欢你
Your references all seem to love you.
烤奶酪是我的拿手
I make a mean grilled cheese.
你想知道秘密配方吗
You want to know the secret ingredients?
好啊
Sure.
腌菜和芥末
Pickles and mustard.
嘣 完成
Boom. Done.
那么 呃 你下周就开始工作吗
Well, uh... can you start next week?
艾玛就快放假了
Emma's about to begin her spring break.
当然 你想什么时候开始我就...
Sure. I can start whenever you need-
呃 格罗斯曼先生
Uh, Mr. Grossman?
这是昙花计划
Here are the steagle plans,
在五分钟后你会有一个关于材料的电话
and you have a materials call in five minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有想说的吗
Is there anything else?
没有了
Nope.
你还有什么问题吗
Is there anything you want to ask me?
你女儿她性格怎么样
What's your daughter like?
艾玛她...做事很专心
Emma is... very focused.
虽然只是个小女孩 但她总是能专心做事
She's a normal little girl, but she can be very focused.
我都不知道如何形容了
I don't know how else to say it.
她很聪明 成绩全优 从没惹过麻烦
She's smart, straight A's, never gets into trouble...
喜欢热巧克力
loves hot chocolate.
是个乖女孩
My kinda girl.
我也觉得
Mine, too.
你的妻子呢
And your wife?
我能和她见见面吗
Should I meet with her, too?
她在艾玛出生后就去世了
She died just after Emma was born.
我深表同情
I'm so sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以 就我们两人相依为命 互相照顾
So it's uh, it's just the two of us and um... we manage.
那么 我们下周见
Well, I guess I will see you next week.
我很期待
Looking forward to it.
你手表酷毙了
Your watch is sick.
是吗
Right?
这是我的生日礼物
I got it for my birthday.
我生日时也收到过手表
I got a watch for my birthday too.
但我不怎么戴
I don't really wear it.
小心点
Careful there!
到你抓了
You're it!
凯蒂 你还好吗
Katie, are you alright?
你还好吗
Are you ok?
抱歉 我不是故意的
I'm so sorry, I didn't mean to hurt you.
来 我扶你起来
Here, let me help you up.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
到谁抓了
Who's it?
还是你 快跑
You're still it, let's go!
瞧我给你带来了什么
I brought you your favourite.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, daddy.
需要我指导吗
You want to read together?
不用了 爸爸
We don't have to, daddy.
我知道你很忙
I know how busy you are.
如果我给你个拥抱 你会给我什么
What would you give me for a basket of hugs?
给你一个吻
A basket of kisses.
给你一个吻 给你一个吻
A basket of kisses. A basket of kisses.
给你一个吻
A basket of kisses.
你看起来真像个小明星
You look like a movie star.
别让我迟到了 爸爸
Don't make me late, dad.
不会的
I won't.
礼服不错 麦洛
Nice suit, Milo.
谢谢
Thanks.
他一直盼望着这一天的到来呢
He has been counting down the days.
哦 可不是吗
Oh, tell me about it.
现在是颁奖时刻
And now, our final award.
圣奥尔登奖章
The St. Alden's Citizenship Medallion.
每年我们都会颁给一位最有个性的
Every year we honour someone of character.
一位真正代表着
Someone who truly embodies the values
学校价值观的人
that this school was founded on.
今年我很荣幸将
This year I am proud to award
圣奥尔登奖章颁发给麦洛·柯蒂斯
the St. Alden's Citizenship Medallion to Milo Curtis.
你真棒
Good job.
给你 麦洛 你真棒
Here you go, Milo. Good job.
谢谢
Thanks!
哇
Wow!
很抱歉我错过了家长会
I'm sorry I missed your parent-teacher conference,
我在城里有个重要的工程
I had a big installation in the city.
别担心 我们可以改时间
No worries. We can reschedule.
艾玛表现得如何
How is Emma doing?
我并不想为难你
I mean, not to put you on the spot.
嗯
Right.
她挺好的
She's fine.
她 呃 我得说
She's um... I have to say,
我教书20年
I've never met anyone quite like her
从没见过像她这样的孩子
in my 20 years of teaching.
为什么听起来像是件坏事
Why does that sound like a bad thing?
不 我没有那个意思
No, I didn't mean that in any fashion at all.
艾玛她有很多优点
Emma's never had one mark against her
而且她还是班上的优等生
and she's one of our top students.
她都可以当班长了
She can be a real leader when she wants to be.
但是呢
But?
她活在自己独特的世界里
Emma lives in her own particular world
但是那世界不是像
and I'm sure it isn't anything like the world
你我活着的这个世界一样
that you and I live in.
我是说 她拥有许多对孩子来说
I mean, she has many remarkable qualities
非常优秀的卓越品质
that are great in a child.
她的勇气是最难得的
Her courage is most unusual.
她没有任何生理恐惧
She's almost without any physical fear.
而且必要时她能给人留下深刻的印象
And she really knows how to come across when she has to.
我打赌她能成为一名演员
She can be an actress, I bet.
算了吧 演员就算了
Please, not an actress.
好吧
Alright.
埃利斯老师
Mrs. Ellis.
噢 嗨 失陪了
Oh, hi. Excuse me.
好吧
Sure.
我真替你骄傲 小甜熊 我知道你很失望
I'm proud of you, honey bear. I know you're disappointed.
那奖牌本来应该属于我
That medal's mine. I deserve it.
麦洛甚至都不敢当着全班的面说话
Milo can't even talk in front of the class.
艾玛
Emma.
每个人都有他们的特长
Everybody has something special to offer.
麦洛是个好孩子
Milo's a good kid.
是吗
Yeah?
但他就是个糟糕的演讲者
Well, he's an awful public speaker.
他连拼写都不会
And he can't spell.
艾玛
Emma.
你说的对
You're right.
对不起
Sorry.
麦洛是我的朋友
Milo's my friend.
我很开心他赢得了奖牌
I'm really happy he got it.
被你说对了 这里简直太酷了
You're right, this place is cool!
我们应该回去了
We should go back now.
艾玛 你怎么了
Emma, what's wrong?
你想干嘛
What do you want?
你应该知道我要干嘛
I think you know.
一二三
One, two, three.
不错 我会发邮箱给你的
That's good, I'll email it to you.
嘿 爸 我们能回家了吗
Hey dad, can we get going?
当然
Sure.
你知道麦洛去哪了吗
Has anyone seen Milo?
我没看到他
I haven't seen him.
艾玛 你见到他了吗
Emma, have you seen him?
呃 之前看到他是在篝火那里
Um, the last place I saw him was by the bonfire.
救命啊 救命啊
Help! Help!
快点
Quickly!
哦 我的天哪
Oh my god!
麦洛 麦洛
MiloMilo?
醒醒 醒醒 宝贝 醒醒啊
Come on, come on, baby! Breathe!
快帮帮我们
Somebody do something!
打报警电话
Call 911!
麦洛
Milo!
醒醒 麦洛 醒醒
Come on, Milo. Come on.
麦洛
Milo?
快救救孩子
Somebody help us!
可怜的孩子
That poor kid.
在他们来抬走他之前
He was lying there on the rocks for hours
他在岩石上躺了几个小时
before they came and took him away.
太可怕了
It was horrible.
她还好吗
How is she?
她还好
She's ok.
她应该是受到惊吓了
I think she's in shock.
我们都被吓到了
I think we all are.
她在楼上看书
She's up in her room, reading.
这件事可能会成为她的阴影
I'm sure it'll hit her later.
嗯 但愿不会这样
Yes, I'm sure it will.
艾玛
Emma.
早上好 爸爸
Morning, dad.
早上好 亲爱的
Morning, hon.
你要麦片吗
Do you want some cereal?
还有剩的
There's just enough left.
不用了 谢谢
No, I'm ok, thanks.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
我很好
I'm alright.
希望今天不会下雨
I hope it doesn't rain today.
我是说昨天的事
I meant about yesterday.
你一定很难过吧
You must be pretty sad, right?
如果你想倾诉 我会听你说的
If you want to talk about it I'm here for you.
好啊
Ok.
你想和我谈谈吗
Do you need someone to talk to?
我不觉得有什么好谈的
I don't really think there's anything to talk about.
给她点时间 孩子的处理方法不同
Give her time. Kids process differently.
别让她为难
Don't make her feel self-conscious.
你可能是对的
You're probably right.
她就是很要强 知道吗
She's just so strong, you know?
我是说 她的老师都这么说
I mean, even her teachers were talking about it.
我只是希望她能花点时间...然后
I just hope that she can take some time and... feel.
瞧瞧是谁来了
Look who's here.
顺便说一句 干得好
Great job, by the way.
她看起来很不错
She seems perfect.
米勒说她和萨姆相处得很好
Miller said she was great with Sam.
我就是专业猎人
Professional head hunter, that's me.
你是想约我朋友利兹出去吗
Are you gonna finally take my friend Lizzy out?
哦老天 你真是没完没了啊
Oh my god, you are relentless.
没错 我会约她的
Yes, I will call her.
嘿 你好
Hey there.
我的任务是什么
Let's get this party started.
这是洗衣机 这是干衣机
Washer, dryer, obviously.
哇 这里太棒了
Wow, this place is amazing.
谢谢
Thanks.
是艾玛出生前
It was a fixer-upper my wife and I bought
妻子和我买的旧房子
right before Emma was born.
这是你妻子吗
Was this your wife?
哦 没错
Oh, yeah.
那是某一年的圣诞贺卡
That was our Christmas card one year.
她来了
There she is.
艾玛 这是克洛伊
Emma, this is Chloe.
克洛伊 这是艾玛
Chloe, this is Emma.
嗨 艾玛
Hi Emma.
很高兴见到你
It's very nice to meet you.
你的项链不错
I like your necklace.
你想看看我的奖牌吗
Do you want to see my medals?
我们得先参观完房子
We have to finish the tour first.
好了 这是紧急报警器
Anyway, emergency numbers here,
所有的钥匙都放在那个小地方
all the keys go in that uh, little place there.
呃 灭火器在洗涤槽的下面
Um, fire extinguisher is under the sink.
楼上卧室也有几个...
We have a couple upstairs in the bedrooms...
我想看电影
I wanna watch a movie.
风吹开了窗户
The wind was blowing a window open.
我关好窗就下来
I'll be down in a minute.
电视播出的影片为《百纳衣到华服》 由孩子们扮演大人
艾尔玛
Elmer!
奈儿
Nell!
看不懂 这太蠢了
I don't get it. This is stupid.
什么蠢
What's stupid?
秀兰·邓波儿
Shirley Temple.
她可是一名美国大使
The woman was a United States ambassador.
不敢想象她有多蠢
I can't imagine she was very stupid.
我是说电影
I meant the movie.
爸爸什么时候回来
When's my dad coming home?
快了
Soon.
他在开会
He has a meeting.
你会为那个溺水的孩子伤心吗
So are you sad about the kid that drowned?
我伤不伤心没什么关系
I don't think it matters if I'm sad.
反正他都死了
He's dead, anyway.
况且 爸爸说我看到他溺水的时候面无表情
Besides, my dad said you don't feel anything when you drown
那你真是无忧无虑 是吧
You're all warm and fuzzy, aren't you?
那你喜欢些什么
So what're you into?
音乐
Music?
骑马
Horses?
我都喜欢
I'm into everything.
你爸怎么样 有女朋友吗
What's the deal with your dadGot a girlfriend?
没有 怎么了
No. Why?
就问问 没什么大不了
Just asking, no biggie.
他有段时间交过一个
He had one for a while.
我不喜欢她
I didn't like her.
所以你爸甩了她吗
So he dumped her?
嗯
Yep.
你真是个让我捉摸不透的人啊
You're sorta something else, aren't you?
那你就是个小偷
And you're sort of a thief.
你在说什么
Excuse me?
而且还挺聪明
And you're smart.
我刚看见你从我爸爸卧室拿走了药
I saw you take the pills from my dad's bedroom.
但是又不足以让我爸爸注意到
But not enough for my dad to notice.
别担心 我不会说的
Don't worry, I won't tell.
我想我今晚就不用按时睡觉了
I think I'm gonna stay up past my bedtime tonight.
你现在去给我拿点冰淇淋
Now go and get me some ice cream.
你个小婊子
You little bitch.
顺便再给我拿点饼干
And bring me a couple of cookies while you're at it.
没事了
It's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我深表遗憾
I'm so sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
感谢到来
Thanks for coming.
嘿 艾玛
Hi, Emma.
噢 别问我怎么样了
Oh, don't ask me how I am.
我不想骗你
I don't wanna lie to you.
仪式很棒
It was a beautiful service.
他也度过了他的最后一日
He had a good last day.
一个非常好的日子
A really good last day.
我是说 他以前从未赢过什么
I mean, he has never won anything before
而他对那奖牌感到特别骄傲
and he was so proud of that medal.
我只想知道那奖牌哪里去了
I just wish I knew where it was.
你没有拿到奖牌吗
You don't have the medal?
呃 可能是沉入海底了吧
Well, I think maybe it sunk to the bottom.
我能为你做些什么吗
Is there anything I can do for you?
我想要一些他那天的照片
If you have any pictures of that day I'd like them.
一些他开心的照片
Pictures of him playing, happy.
这算最好的帮助了
It really does help.
爸爸
Dad?
你在我房间干什么
What're you doing in my room?
就收拾一下
Just picking up a little.
但这里很整齐
It is picked up.
一直都很整齐
It's always picked up.
还有事吗
Anything else?
没了
No.
埃利斯老师
Miss Ellis.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
相信我 我们建校95年来
Believe me, nothing like this has ever happened
从未发生过这种事
in our 95-year history
而我们调用了手头上的一切资源
and we're using every resource we have
确保这种事不会再发生
to make sure that it never happens again.
但是有些法律问题我们必须处理下
But there is a legal issue that we have to contend with.
请便
Sure.
我们联系了所有的家长
We're reaching out to all the parents to gather
收集一切能收集到的情报
whatever information we can.
呃 好吧 我 我听不太懂
Well, ok, I- I don't really understand.
所以这是保险之类的 还是...
So this is an insurance thing, or...?
没错 那是其中之一
That's one component, yes.
那么 究竟发生了什么
Well, what did happen?
也没人和大家说具体情况
No one's given anybody an update.
麦洛怎么摔下悬崖的
How did Milo fall off that cliff?
这就是我们想弄清楚的
That's what we're gonna find out.
有警察介入吗
Are the police involved?
我们无权透露
We're not at liberty to share that.
显然 如果警察介入调查时
Obviously, if and when the authorities are involved,
有些家庭可能会不得安宁
we may share that information with the families.
有些家庭
Some families.
抱歉 你们是不是有什么瞒着我
Excuse me, but is there something you're not telling me?
请别误会
Please don't misunderstand.
我们只是想得到事情的真相
We're just trying to get to the facts.
但是我们必须知道艾玛听见或看见了什么
But if Emma heard or saw something, we need to know.
那男孩不会游泳 他还怕水
That boy couldn't swim and he was afraid of water.
他为什么要去海岸岩壁上面
Why was he out on the rocks?
你个小混球
You little shit.
艾玛是最后一个见过那男孩的
Any information would be helpful
她知道的消息对我们有很大帮助
as it seems Emma was the last to see the boy.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
至少有三个人看见她在岩壁边
At least three people saw her near the rock face.
现在 我们不是在说艾玛做了错事
Now, we're not saying Emma did anything wrong
呃 我希望没有
Well, I should hope not.
听着 我会注意你说的话
Listen, I'd be very careful what you insinuate.
艾玛
Emma?
Emma?!
艾玛
Emma!
怎么了
What happened?
你还好吗
Are you ok?
我们先走了
We'll show ourselves out.
好 好的
Yeah, sure.
好了
Ok.
让我看看你的手
Let me see this arm.
看看
Let's see it.
好了 我给你清理清理
Alright, let's get you cleaned up.
好了
Ok?
很庆幸你没有刮得很严重 小甜熊
You are lucky you didn't cut yourself worse, honey bear.
对不起 爸爸
I'm sorry, daddy.
没事的
It's ok.
意外经常发生
Accidents happen.
你知道埃利斯老师来了吗
Do you know why Mrs. Ellis was here?
是来问麦洛的事吧
It was about Milo I bet.
告诉我那一天你到底发生了什么
Is there anything you wanna tell me about that day?
什么都行
Anything at all?
没有
Nope.
你确定
You're sure?
你从未去过岩壁那 对吧
You weren't ever out on that rock face, were you?
没有
No.
埃利斯老师说你有
Mrs. Ellis says you were.
她撒谎
She's lying.
亲爱的 埃利斯老师为什么要撒谎呢
Honey, why would Mrs. Ellis lie?
因为她讨厌我
Because she hates me.
她一直都不喜欢我
She never liked me.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
她为什么要那么说
Why would she say that?
我 我不知道发生了什么
I- I don't know what's going on,
我只...我只是担心你
I'm just... just worried about you.
对不起 爸爸
I'm sorry, daddy.
我不是有意的
I don't mean to get upset.
我只是因为麦洛而伤心
I'm just sad about Milo.
想让我给你讲故事吗
Want me to read to you?
我没有那心情
I'm not really in the mood.
好吧
Ok.
爸爸
Daddy?
给你一个吻 你会给我什么
What would you give me for a basket of kisses?
一个拥抱
A basket of hugs.
嗨
Hi.
抱歉 我只是想来看看艾玛
Sorry, I was just checking on you and Emma.
还有牛奶喝完了
And we're out of milk.
嘿
Hey.
呃 很抱歉
Um, I'm sorry.
昨晚我不是有意吓你的
I didn't mean to startle you last night.
我本来可以写个购物清单的
I probably could have waited to do the market list.
嗯
Yeah.
有事吗
So what's up?
不介意的话 我可以在这里抽烟吗
Um, hey, do you mind if I, like, smoke in here?
我不能在艾玛身边抽 在这里应该可以吧
I would never do it around Emma but out here I thought maybe?
你看见墙上的东西了吗
Can you see everything against that wall?
都是易燃品
It's all flammable.
所以不可以 这里不是抽烟的最佳地点
So no, I don't think this is the best place for a smoking area.
好 知道了
Ah. Got it.
还有其它事吗
So how can I help ya?
艾玛的伤口好了
Emma's arm seems good.
抱歉 我本来应该看住她的
I'm sorry, I should have been paying closer attention to her.
原本还和她在一起
I was with her one minute
我一转身她就不见了
and when I turned around she was gone.
是的
Yeah.
我知道 这些事难免的
I understand, stuff happens.
就是这样
Stuff happens.
没错 确实
Hell yeah, it does.
那么 你和艾玛相处得怎么样
So let me ask you, how are things with you and Emma?
一切都好吗
Everything ok?
哦 她很棒
Oh, she's great.
很酷的孩子
Such a cool kid.
那就好
That's good to hear.
她特别...幽默、聪明
She's so... fun and smart.
很有趣
And funny.
艾玛和有趣可不能相提并论
I never would have thought of Emma as funny.
这不是简单的有趣
Oh, not in a weird way.
她有趣在...
She's funny like...
不清楚 就是与众不同
I don't know, like different.
好的方面
In a good way.
和她同龄女孩都很无聊
Most girls her age are pretty lame.
到处是紫色紧身裤和公主海报
Purple leggings and princess posters everywhere,
但艾玛就像个淑女 知道吗
but Emma is like... a lady, you know?
那当然
I do know.
我刚才看了你妻子的一些照片
Oh, I was looking at more pictures of your wife.
她身材真火辣
She was pretty hot.
对 没错
Yes, she was.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
得赶走这些黄蜂了
Gotta get rid of these wasps.
那我得回去看看艾玛了
Well, I better get back to Emma.
她想开滑板车
She wants to go on the scooter.
挺好
Great.
总之 我很喜欢这份工作
Anyway, I love my job here.
我只想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
谢谢 这么说我很高兴
Thank you, I appreciate that.
艾玛也是这么想的
I'm sure Emma does, as well.
是的
Yeah.
我们相处的很好
We love each other.
你爸觉得你惹出大麻烦了 小卷毛
Your dad thinks you have major issues, Curly Sue.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
他知道那件事了
He knows what's up.
他在拷问我关于你的事
He was grilling me about you.
他问了什么
What'd he ask?
你很在意吗
Wouldn't you like to know?
别担心 我当着他的面夸你呢
Don't worry, I told him how great you are.
我挺你 小妹
I got you, girl.
别惹我就行
Just don't mess with me.
为什么老师会来麦洛家
Why is Mrs. Ellis at Milo's?
你不会是害怕了吧
You must be shitting bricks.
恶心
Gross.
你为什么要那样说
Why would you say something like that?
因为他们在调查你 宝贝
'Cause they're closing in on you now, babe.
来搜寻证据
Building their case.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
总有一天警察会介入调查
One day the police will get involved
然后就会拷问是不是你害了麦洛
and you'll have to come clean about what you did to Milo.
我才没有害麦洛
I didn't do anything to Milo.
你当然没有
Sure you didn't.
总之 等着瞧吧
Anyway, you'll see.
你还是先把谎话编好
You better get your story straight
不然你就会被抓走
or you're gonna get busted.
这要是我 也会害怕的
Yeah, I would be worried too if I were you.
我才没害怕呢
I'm not worried about anything.
你只是太婊了
You're just being a bitch.
听着
Look,
我不知道你岩壁边对麦洛做了什么
I don't know what you did to that kid on the rocks
但这肯定不是什么好事
but I know it wasn't good,
我知道你对他们都说谎了
and I know you're lying to everybody.
而你在爸爸房间偷东西
And you stole from my dad's room.
哇 我想我们都有不可告人的秘密了
Well I guess we both have secrets to keep for each other,
对吧
don't we?
我爸爸说有秘密不好
My dad says it's not good to keep secrets.
必须得实话实说
If you see something you should tell.
你是在威胁我吗 小甜熊
Are you threatening me, honey bear?
知道他们怎么对待进监狱的孩子吗
Do you know what they do to kids that go to jail?
不想知道
Not really.
如果是偷了东西或者伤害了别人
Well, if it's something like stealing or hurting someone
你会被送进医院 那里的孩子很可怕
you get sent to a hospital where kids yell
会尖叫 还会自残
and scream and cut themselves.
你永远也出不来
You never get out.
但是如果你闯了大祸
But if it's something really bad,
比如把人...杀死
like maybe if someone... dies,
你就会被送上电椅
you get sent to the electric chair.
你傻了吧
You're silly.
他们才不会把孩子送上电椅
Nobody would put a kid in the electric chair.
他们当然会
Sure they do.
知道他们把你送上电椅会干什么吗
Do you know what happens in the electric chair?
会烤了你
It cooks you.
你皮肤会噼啪响然后萎缩
Your skin crackles and shrivels
就像早上烤培根
like when we make bacon in the morning.
我才不信你
I don't believe you.
小孩都坐不上那么大的椅子
A kid wouldn't even fit in that big chair.
他们有专门给小孩的电椅
They have a special one for kids.
甚至还刷上粉色 下面还放着
It's even painted pink and they put pee-pee pads underneath
当你吓尿时用的尿垫
for when you piss yourself.
天呐 你真恶心
God, you're disgusting.
网上搜
Google it.
艾玛
Emma?
Em?
艾玛
Emma?
艾玛 你在外面吗
Emma, are you out there?
艾玛
Emma?
有人吗
Hello?
她在这里啊
There she is.
你今天过得有趣吗
How was your dayYou do anything fun?
呃 我不确定有不有趣
Well, I don't know if it was fun exactly,
但过得不错
but I had a good day.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
哦 没什么
Oh, nothing.
你手上拿着什么
What's in your hand?
没什么
Nothing.
哦 艾玛
Oh, Emma.
这是哪来的
Where did this com from?
艾玛
Emma?
麦洛的奖牌怎么会在我们家
How did Milo's medal get into this house?
我...我不知道
I... I don't know.
你在哪里找到的
Where did you find it?
就藏在床底下
It was hidden under the bed.
我打扫的时候找到的
I found it cleaning.
谢谢 克洛伊
Thank you, Chloe.
我想和艾玛单独谈谈
I need to talk to Emma alone.
那请便
Sure thing.
艾玛
Emma?
麦洛的奖牌为什么会在你的床下
How did Milo Curtis's medal get under your bed?
我不知道它就在我床下
I don't know how it got there.
我怎么知道为什么在我床下
How should I know how it got there?
你是不是什么时候去了岩壁那...
Were you ever, at any time, out on that rock face?
有 爸爸
Yes, daddy.
我去过那里
I went there once.
那埃利斯老师是不是并没有说谎
So Mrs. Ellis wasn't lying when she said you were there.
她应该没说谎
I guess she wasn't lying.
应该 爸爸
Yes, daddy.
是不是和麦洛在一起
Were you with Milo?
待了一会
For a minute.
然后发生了什么
And what happened?
艾玛
Emma!
这事很严重 我不知道真相的话
This is very serious and I can't help you
我就帮不了你
if I don't know the truth.
麦洛和我玩了一个游戏
Milo and I were playing a game we made up.
类似于夺旗游戏
It was kinda like Capture the Flag,
只是用他的奖牌当旗子
but with his medal instead.
我赢了 所以他给我戴了一下奖牌
I won, so Milo gave me his medal to wear.
所以他是在岩壁外给你的奖牌吗
So he gave you the medal out on the rock?
不
No.
我之后拿的
I got it later on.
然后我就不知道麦洛去哪了
I don't know where Milo went after that.
艾玛
Emma.
你知道柯蒂斯女士一直在找这个
Do you know that Mrs. Curtis has been looking for this?
她想把奖牌和麦洛一起安葬
She wanted to bury Milo with it.
这太蠢了
That's stupid.
麦洛才不会知道有没有埋下奖牌
Milo wouldn't even know if he was buried with it or not.
爸爸
Daddy?
怎么了
What's wrong?
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我只想透透气
I just need some air.
嘿 安琪 是我
Hey, Ange, it's me.
听着 我需要一个
Listen, I need the name
给艾玛看病的精神科医生
of a good child psychiatrist for Emma.
并不是急事
It's nothing urgent,
我只是想让她找个人倾诉一下
I just think that she needs someone to talk to.
我这有个不错的人选
Ok. I have the perfect person.
太棒了
Oh, ok.
好 谢谢了
Good, thanks.
那我等会再打给你
Um, I'll call you back.
二位先生和女士
Mr. and Mrs. Grossman,
你们的女儿有点问题
there's something wrong with your daughter.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好像有东西在喷水池那
I think I saw something in the fountain.
谁干的
Who did this?
觉得自己小有成就 对吧
Pretty happy with yourself, aren't ya?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你知道我什么意思
You know exactly what I mean.
不 我真听不懂
Nope, I really don't.
是说我把麦洛的奖牌藏在你爸房间吗
Oh, you mean I shit-boxed you with Milo's medal?
你真恶心
You're so gross.
吃你的鸡蛋
Eat your eggs.
真为你感到遗憾
I feel bad for you.
是我的话我才不想去
I wouldn't wanna go do this.
我也不想去
And I don't want to.
是我我就什么都不说
I wouldn't say anything.
这件事你不会有好下场的
Nothing good can come of this for you.
我忘了我是在和谁说话了
I forgot who I was dealing with.
你会没事的
You'll be just fine.
你个小贱人
You little psycho.
艾玛
Emma?
我们该走了
We have to go.
很高兴见到你 艾玛
It's good to see you, Emma.
我每次见到麦洛就会让我想起
Any time I see one of Milo's classmates it reminds me
他有多少朋友还有他是多好的孩子
of how many friends he had and what a good person he was.
你假期过得怎么样
How's your school break going?
还行 谢谢
Fine, thank you.
柯蒂斯女士 我们有东西想给你
Mrs. Curtis, we have something that we wanna give to you.
你哪里弄来的
Where did you find that?
是麦洛让艾玛戴了一会儿
Apparently Milo let Emma wear it for a while and...
然后 看他没回来 她就留着了
and then, when he... didn't come back she kept it.
她现在知道错了 她会道歉的
She knows it was wrong and she wants to apologize,
对吧 艾玛
isn't that right, Emma?
是的
That's right.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
我不该留着的
I shouldn't have kept it.
我不明白
I don't understand.
为什么麦洛会给你戴
Milo gave it to you to wearWhy?
就是个游戏
It was a game.
我正准备还给他 他却...
I was gonna give it back, but he...
我再也没见到他
I never saw him again.
呃 我不知道该说什么了
Well, I don't know what to say.
很高兴你把它带给了我
I'm glad you brought it back to me.
我这一整天...
This whole day is...
都为埃利斯老师的事惶恐不安
I'm still in shock about Mrs. Ellis.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
她去世了
She's dead.
她在格伦瓦尔大道出了车祸
She rolled her car on Glenvale Avenue
在这之前还在这里谈麦洛的事
and she was just here talking about Milo.
我 我不知道
I- I didn't know.
我深感遗憾 爸爸
I'm really sad, daddy.
埃利斯老师是我最爱的老师
Mrs. Ellis was my favourite teacher.
她是怎么出车祸的
Do we know how it happened?
电视上说她车上有黄蜂窝
On the TV it said there was a wasp's nest in her car.
她被黄蜂给蛰了 然后才出的车祸
It was a science project or something and she was stung.
我也不明白黄蜂窝为什么会在她车上
I don't know, it doesn't make any sense to me.
爸爸 我不太舒服
Daddy, I'm not feeling well.
能回家了吗
Can we go home?
当然
Sure.
所以我们现在不用再提
So now we don't have to talk about Milo
麦洛了 对吧
ever again, right?
那我得快点了 爸爸
I'm gonna run, daddy.
克洛伊今天要和我做纸杯蛋糕
Chloe and I are baking cupcakes today.
儿 童 的 异 常 行 为
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
不 自 然  的  的  表  情
缺 乏 同 情 心
自  恋
虚  伪
控  制  欲
危 险 的 疾 病
包 括 精 神 病
嘿
Hey.
我们马上就要去医生那里了
We gotta leave soon for our doctor's appointment.
我快好了
I'll be ready.
爸爸 我在想 你说得对
Daddy, I was thinking, you're right.
我想这对我来说会有好处的
I think something good will come of this.
我也希望
I hope so.
艾玛 我给准备了一些你喜欢的东西
Emma, I have some magazines on the table you might like
马奇医生的扮演者 帕特里夏·麦科马克 曾扮演过1956年版《坏种》小女主
桌上有杂志
while you wait.
可以的话 我得先和你爸爸
I'm just gonna have a little chat with your dad,
谈一会
if that's ok.
当然可以 马奇医生
Yeah, of course, Dr. March.
那么
So.
需要我帮你们什么
How can I help you and Emma?
我不知道
I don't know.
呃...
Um...
关于你女儿 你觉得哪里最烦恼
Well, what is your primary concern?
艾玛从小就与众不同
Emma has always been different.
很大部分是好的那种不同 但是同时
Very, very much in a good way, but also...
会有一股...冷漠
there's a... coldness.
我不知道如何形容
I don't know how to say it.
呃 缺乏感情
Um, a lack of emotion.
我是说 她有感情 但是 呃
I mean, she has emotions, but uh,
她会笑会哭什么的
she laughs and cries and all that,
但是会 呃...
but it can be um...
我不清楚
I don't know.
她对我撒谎 让我有点不相信她
She's lying to me and I don't trust her anymore.
对于她这么大的孩子来说撒谎是常见的
Well, it's very common for children her age to lie.
大多数孩子会与内心情感作斗争
Most kids struggle with their emotions.
通常情况下 他们都不知道该如何
They very often don't know how or what they should be feeling
展露自己的情绪
at any point in time.
对于家长负担是挺大的
It can be very taxing on a parent.
很多人都认为事情的严重性
Mr. Grossman, everyone thinks their issues
比实际意义上的更大
are bigger than they are.
更独特
More unique.
但还是会有罕见情况
Obviously there are the rare cases,
我也曾见过一种心理疾病
and I've had them, of real psychological illness.
总之 我很期待和艾玛谈话
Anyway, I'm looking forward to talking to Emma.
那么 我不是那种给人做手术
So, I'm not that kind of doctor who operates on people
之类的医生 我是那种...
or things like that, I'm what's called-
你是心理医生
You're a shrink.
哇 原来你知道啊
Well, you know that term.
我看过《介入》
I watch Intervention.
哦 好吧
Oh, yes.
那么 我是精神科医生 这是个名词 就是帮助...
Well, I'm a psychiatrist, which is a fancy word for someone
那些有心理疾病的病人
to talk to who can help you sort things out.
我没有什么心理疾病
I don't really need anything sorted out.
真的吗
Really?
为什么没有呢
Well, why is that?
我是说 大多数人都会有的
I mean, most people have something that they would like
每个人的都不一样
to be different.
我没有
I don't.
啊 我懂了
Ah, I see.
我理解你对麦洛的悲痛
I understand that your friend Milo recently passed away.
说得没错
That's right.
你对这件事的感受如何
How did that make you feel?
我肯定你很难受吧
Pretty sad, I bet.
我哭了两天
I cried for two days.
哦
Oh.
我理解你
I understand.
这是你第一次看到认识的人去世吗
Was that the first time someone you knew died?
不是
No.
哦
Oh.
明白了
I see.
马奇医生
Dr. March?
为什么人去世时 他身边的人会伤心呢
Why do people get so upset when people die?
这事迟早会发生在每个人身上啊
It's gonna happen to everyone sooner or later.
问得好 艾玛
It's a great question, Emma.
我们知道这事不可逆 但依旧会很痛心
We all do know it's inevitable and we grieve anyway.
为他而感到同情
To feel or to have empathy for others
这是我们人的本性
is what it means to be human.
艾玛 我要告诉你个秘密
Emma, I'm going to tell you a secret.
我像你那么大的时候我也这么做过
I did the exact same things as you when I was your age.
你们俩看起来挺融洽嘛
Well, you two seemed to really hit it off.
我们谈的很畅快 是吧 艾玛
Oh, we had a great talk, didn't we, Emma?
当然
Yes.
爸爸 我能出去玩会吗
Daddy, can I go outside?
当然
Sure.
格罗斯曼先生 我在职业生涯里见过
Mr. Grossman, I have seen thousands of kids
许多孩子
in my practise,
艾玛是我遇到的最正常的孩子
and Emma seems 100 percent perfectly average.
实际上 和她聊天让我想起了小时候
In fact, I told her she reminds me of myself.
你好
Hey there.
嘿
Hey.
检查得怎么样
How'd the appointment go?
很好
Fine.
艾玛在楼上
Emma's up in her room.
那么 我得穿上衣服
Well, I guess I better put on some clothes,
上去看看了
head up there.
希望你不会介意我趁机晒晒太阳
I hope you don't mind me taking advantage of the sun.
不 你得抓紧时间好好享受
No, you... gotta take advantage of it.
确实得抓紧时间
Gotta take advantage.
没错
Yep.
你没有朋友吗
Don't you have any friends?
关你什么事
What do you care?
显然大家都认为你有精神病
Clearly everyone thinks you're mental.
随你怎么说
Whatever, Chloe.
现在大家都知道
Now that everyone knows
你偷了那孩子的奖牌 只是时间问题
you stole that dead kid's medal it's just a matter of time.
什么时间问题
A matter of time until what?
调查出你对他做了什么
They find out what you did to him.
我听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
也许你马上就会被送上电椅了
Maybe you'll end up in the little pink chair.
我马上让爸爸赶走你
I'm gonna have my dad get rid of you.
去啊
Go for it.
他可不会听你的
He won't do it.
你爸爸看上我了
Your dad and I understand each other.
随便你怎么像疯子一样盯着我
You can give me that psycho stare all you want
但告诉你个事实 你爸是个痴男
but the fact is this: your dad's a DILF.
我要定他了 懂吗
D-I-L-F, ok?
他还是单身 他刚才还在打量我身材呢
And he's single, and he was totally just scoping me out.
他和我搞在一起 你不介意吧
You wouldn't mind if he and I hooked up, would you?
可怜的小家伙 放松点
The poor guy needs a release.
我是说 他真不错
I mean, just look at him.
离我爸爸远点
Stay away from my dad.
不然呢
Or what?
我不能做你的继母吗
Wouldn't I make a good stepmom?
你吓不到我的 小不点
You don't scare me, little girl.
我不管 你就只是站在一边
I don't care if you stood there
看着那小孩子淹死
and watched that little kid drown,
还是你把他推下去的
or even if you pushed him in.
在我那 就你这种宠坏的小贱种
Where I come from a spoiled little princess like you
就算是个屁 相信我
ain't nothing, believe me.
威胁别人可不好
It's not nice to threaten people.
但我在你眼里
But you and me?
也不算什么好人 对吧
We're not nice, are we?
噢 艾玛 你吓到我了
Oh, Emma, you scared me.
你喜欢克洛伊吗
Do you like Chloe?
等等 什么
Wait, what?
她说你喜欢她
She said that you like her.
说你 看上她了
That you... understand each other.
她还说她想做我的继母
She said she could be my stepmother some day.
哇 哇 哇
Woah, woah, woah.
等等 让我缓缓
Wait, hold on a second.
首先 这件事绝不可能
First of all, that would never happen,
其次 她为什么要这么说
and why would she say something like that?
你自己清楚
You tell me.
艾玛
Emma.
我不想要继母
I don't want a stepmother.
绝不想
Ever.
没你想象的那么严重
Everything's gonna be ok.
我有约会 不过很快会回来的
I have a meeting but I'll be home early, ok?
回来再说
Then we'll talk.
好吧 我等你回来
Great. I'll wait up.
约会愉快
Have fun on your date!
所以你没再结过婚
So you never remarried?
没有
Nope.
你有多喜欢玩转情场
You like playing the field that much, huh?
简直爱死了
Yeah, I love it.
很让人满足
It's so fulfilling.
你知道吧 特别是抚养一个小女孩
I mean, you know, especially raising a young girl.
很棒
Great.
我开第一家店时折腾了将近四个月
When I first opened the store I had about four months.
我担心店会倒闭 但生意逐渐好了起来
I was really worried but then business picked up
到现在有六年了 都很顺利
and it's been really good for six years now.
艾玛
Emma?
该死的 艾玛
Dammit, Emma.
艾玛
Emma?
Emma!
艾玛 快开门 这可不好玩
Emma, let me out of here. This isn't funny.
艾玛
Emma!
Emma?
艾玛
Emma!
借过一下 这是我的房子
Let me through! This is my house!
艾玛
Emma!
你是房主吗
Are you the homeowner
是的
Yes.
你是房主吗
Are you the homeowner
没错
Yes, yes.
我有个九岁的女儿 她叫艾玛
I have a nine-year-old daughter, her name is Emma,
她和她保姆一起
she's here with her nanny.
先生 你女儿没事
Sir, your daughter is fine,
她和我们副警长在房子里
she's in a house with one of my deputies.
很不幸 发生了这么突然的事
Now, unfortunately there's been a terrible accident.
那个叫克洛伊的保姆
The nanny, Chloe,
当时还在起火的工棚里
was in the work shed when the fire broke out.
她可能被吓到了
I think she's in shock.
她没告诉我们太多 但他说那个保姆
She hasn't told us much but apparently the young woman
在工棚里偷偷抽烟
would sneak a smoke in the work shed.
好了 给你们一点独处时间
Ok, I will give you two a moment.
小甜熊
Honey bear.
没事了 爸爸
It's ok, daddy.
我没事
Nothing happened to me.
艾玛 我知道你醒着
Emma, I know you're awake.
我觉得我们有麻烦了
I think we're in trouble.
我觉得我们惹上大麻烦了
I think we're both in very big trouble,
我们谈谈 你必须告诉我事情的真相
and we need to talk and I need you to tell me the truth.
我是你父亲 我爱你
I'm your father, I love you,
我会竭尽所能来帮你
I'm going to do anything I can to help you.
是你杀了麦洛 对吧
You hurt Milo, didn't you?
是不是
Didn't you?
他要告状说我拿走了他的奖牌
He was gonna tell on me that I took his medal.
我不想伤害他的
I didn't mean to hurt him.
我推了一下 他就摔下去了
When I pushed him, he fell.
他一直喊 喊着说他不会游泳
He kept on yelling, yelling that he couldn't swim,
但我没有相信他
but I didn't believe him.
他老是夸大事实
He always over-exaggerated.
一会他就没有再喊 然后我再也没看到他了
After a while he stopped yelling and I couldn't see him anymore.
对不起 爸爸
I'm so sorry, daddy.
我不想惹麻烦
I didn't want to get into trouble.
我不会再犯了
I won't do it again.
莱薇娅 片头部分提起过
还有莱薇娅 你的第一任保姆
And Mrs. Levia, your first nanny,
你又把她怎么了
what happed to her?
她紧紧抓着我的手
She should have never grabbed my arm,
所以我踢了她 她就摔下了楼梯
so I kicked her, and she fell down the stairs.
我并没做错什么
I didn't do anything wrong.
她是成年人
She's the adult.
她应该更好地保护自己
She should have protected herself better.
那埃利斯老师和黄蜂呢
And Mrs. Ellis and the wasps?
还有今晚 你对克洛伊做了什么
And tonight, what did you do to Chloe?
艾玛
Emma!
警长迟早会发现这事实真相的
The sheriff will get to the bottom of this eventually
所以别再该死地骗我了
so don't give me the bullshit story.
你说了"该死"
You said "bullshit".
艾玛 你知道你会怎么样吗
Emma, do you know what could happen to you?!
知道吗
Do you?!
我们会怎么样
What could happen to us?
知道 爸爸
Yes, daddy.
他们会抓走我然后把我送上
They're gonna take me and they're gonna put me
小椅子 粉色小电椅
in the little chair, the little pink electric chair.
我真的不想去
I really don't wanna go there.
我不想尿到自己身上
I don't wanna pee myself.
艾玛 你在说什么
Emma, what're you talking about?
克洛伊说我伤害麦洛
Chloe said she knew about
这事总有一天会被大家知道
Milo and one day everyone would.
她说他们会把我
She said that they were gonna take me
送上专门放小孩子的电椅
to this little electric chair that they put kids in.
还告诉我说她会做我的继母
She told me she was gonna be my stepmother.
艾玛 冷静
Emma, calm down.
我不想要继母
I don't want a stepmother!
绝不
Ever!
她从你房间偷药片
She stole pills from your room.
我看见了
I watched.
她欺骗你
She fooled you.
你不会做任何事
You weren't gonna do anything about it.
什么都不会
Not one thing!
所以你杀了她
So you did.
是不是这样
Isn't that right?
也是迫不得已
Someone had to.
我是马奇医生
This is Dr. March.
之后两周我可能会不在
I'm out of the office for the next two weeks.
如有急事 可以打报警电话
If this is an emergency please call 911
或打我同事麦兹医生的电话914 555 0113
or you can call my associate, Dr. Metz, at 914-555-0113.
我是大卫
This is David.
你好 格罗斯曼先生 我是彼得森警长
Oh hi, Mr. Grossman, this is Sheriff Peterson.
很抱歉那么早打给你
I'm sorry to call you so early.
只是想问一下你和艾玛还好吗
Just checking to see that you and Emma are doing ok.
嗯
Yeah.
嗯 我们很好 谢谢
Yeah, we're doing ok, thank you.
好 好
Good, good.
还有 我在想 呃
Also, I was wondering uh,
我们什么时候能谈一下
when would be a good time to talk?
我不想打扰你 但我有些问题
I don't want to intrude but there are some questions
想问问你和艾玛 如果可以的话
I need to ask you and Emma, if that's possible.
呃 艾玛有点不舒服
Uh, yeah, Emma's very sick.
你应该知道 她对那场事故很难过
She's upset about the accident as you can imagine,
而我 我今天有很多工作
and I have a... a big day at work.
能先推迟几天吗
Could we postpone maybe for a few days?
周一如何 你和艾玛有空吗
How's Monday, you and Emma?
我去你家
I'll come by the house?
当然
Sure.
那样最好 到时见
That'll be great. I'll see you then.
艾玛
Emma.
收拾东西
Pack your things.
我们要走了
We have to leave.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
湖边小屋
The lake house.
为什么
Why?
你讨厌那里
You hate it there.
我不讨厌那里
I don't hate it there.
你以前说过的
That's what you said once.
还有多久到
How long will we be there?
我不清楚
I don't know.
我们为什么要去那
What're we gonna do there?
我想找个地方冷静冷静
I just need a place to think.
哈哈 又见面了
Ha ha! There he is.
看看你啊
Look at you.
你还是老样子
You haven't changed a bit.
寒酸 困苦 还没装有线电视
Well, cold air, hard work, and no cable tv,
希望你们俩能常住在这
and you too could live forever.
这是我盼望的那个她吗
Hey, is that who I think it is?
不可能 艾玛还只是个孩子
It can't be, 'cause Emma's just a baby
你真是个成熟的女孩
and you're a full grown woman.
很高兴见到你
It's very nice to meet you.
我也很高兴见到你
Nice meeting you, too.
你长得真像你妈妈
You look just like your ma.
我很高兴你们终于回来了
Well, I'm glad you finally got to come up here.
你妹妹安琪拉一直住在这里
Your sister has been bogarting the place.
她如果同意 你们就可以住在这了
Angela would live here full time if she could.
如果有什么需要可以叫我
Well, if you need anything you let me know
我会马上过来
and I'll be right out.
过了这么多年很高兴再见到你 艾玛
And it's uh, good to see you after all the years, Emma.
我也是
You too.
谢了 布莱恩 有需要会叫你
Thanks, Brian. I'll call you if I need you.
好
Alright.
你应该事先打电话给我
You still should have called me David.
那有什么用
What good would that have done?
我没想通
And I wasn't thinking straight.
我现在都还没想通
I'm still not thinking straight.
克洛伊 可怜的女孩
Chloe, that poor girl.
怎么会发生这种事呢
How could such a thing have happened?
警察和消防员怎么说的
What did the police or firefighters say?
他们...还在调查
They're... investigating.
那艾玛怎么样了
Well, how's Emma?
需要我过来帮忙吗
Should I come up to the lake house?
我可以请假
I could take off work.
不 没事的
No, it's fine.
我们只想花点时间安静一下
We're just taking some time away.
好了 我该挂了
Look, I gotta go.
有事给我打电话
Hey, call me.
我很担心你们 大卫
I'm worried about you, David.
喂
Hello?
我们找到起火源了
We've found the source of the fire.
是蓄意纵火
It was deliberately set.
知道是谁干的吗
Do you know who did it?
还不清楚
Not yet,
不过我们已经把证据送往了研究所
but uh, from what we've sent the lab
我们会很快找出凶手的
we'll know pretty soon.
好 明白
Ok, alright.
找到了告诉我
Keep me posted.
好的
Will do.
你不去接吗
Aren't you gonna answer?
一开始只是对宠物下手
The killing started with the family pet,
但随着蒂莫西的成长
but as Timothy grew,
他的犯罪率也逐渐变大
so did his crimes.
马沙洛维茨博士
Dr. Marshalovitz,
一位研究反社会儿童的专家讲解道
an expert on violet child sociopaths explains:
暴力行为似乎存在于他们的内心
The violence seems to be inside them,
像坏种一样深埋着
buried like a bad seed.
最终成长 一旦发芽...
Eventually it grows and once it starts...
就不会再停下
...it doesn't seem to stop.
杀 手 的 特 征
我们得谈谈
非常紧急
- 彼得森警长
艾玛
Emma.
我不希望你这么偷看我
I don't like you sneaking around like that.
你在那里站多久了
How long have you been standing there?
你在偷窥我吗
Were you snooping on me?
我觉得是你在偷窥我
I think you were snooping on me.
我说过了
I told you,
我没做错什么
I didn't do anything wrong.
我绝不会无缘无故伤害别人
I would never hurt anyone for no reason.
我绝对不会那么做
I would never, ever do that.
你觉得我会吗
Do you think I would?
会吗 爸爸
Do you, daddy?
我可不会再信你了
I don't know anymore.
我太失望了
That makes me sad.
为什么
Why?
你为什么要这么对我
Why would you do that to me?
我可是你唯一的亲人
I'm the only person you have.
不
No.
如果你死了我还可以找安琪拉姑姑
If something happened to you I'd live with aunt Angela.
至少她还觉得我不错
At least she thinks I'm nice.
哦 天呐
Oh my god.
插曲：Terrified - Rivvrs
*Pour me a drink,*
给我倒杯酒
*And leave the bottle,*
把瓶子留下
*'Cause I can see no ending in sight,*
因为我看不到尽头
*To this fight,*
这场战斗
*To the war that I wage*
我看不到这场战斗
*with the back of my mind,*
我看不到我用心灵发动的战斗
*Pour me something,*
给我倒点什么
*And keep it coming through the night,*
让它一直流到夜里
*'Cause I am terrified,*
因为我很害怕
*I don't know why,*
我不知为何
*I don't wanna think,*
我不想去思考
*And this whiskey does me right,*
这种威士忌对我很好
*It grips me tighter than any lover has tried,*
它把我抓的比任何一个恋人都紧
我给你带了你最爱喝的
I brought your favourite.
我能加点奶油在上面吗
Can I have whipped cream on it?
当然
Sure.
*I'm always grasping,*
我总是贪婪的
*To something that  I've outlasted,*
抓住一些比我更美好长久的东西
*I'm just the sum of  all my worst habits,*
我只是自己所有坏习惯的总和
新消息
*Intertwined,*
交织在一起
很担心你们啊
打电话给我
可以一起读书吗 爸爸
Do you wanna read together, daddy?
不了吧
I don't think so.
我觉得你该睡了
I think you should just sleep.
你能坐在这陪我入睡吗
Will you sit with me until I fall asleep?
当然 小甜熊
Sure, honey bear.
*I don't know why,*
我不知为何
*I need something,*
我可能需要些什么
医生告诉你妈妈
The doctors told your mommy
说如果她不吃药的话可能会死
that if she didn't take her medicine she might die.
而她却说"只要你向我发誓"
And she said "only if you can promise me
"这不会伤到宝宝"
"it won't hurt my baby".
不管付出什么代价
She always did whatever she wanted to do,
她总是先想到你
no matter what the cost.
你让我想起了她
You remind me of her.
你知道我们要去哪里吗
Do you know where we're gonna go yet?
知道
Yes.
一个宁静的地方
Somewhere safe.
*I'm terrified.*
我吓坏了
*I'm scared to let go.*
我害怕放手
*I don't know why.*
我不知为何
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, daddy.
我也爱你 小甜熊
I love you, too, honey bear.
她想杀了我
Angela, she tried to kill me.
她打开了家里的煤气
She turned on all the gas in the house!
大卫 你说的毫无依据
David, what you're saying doesn't make any sense.
你说的是艾玛吗
You're talking about Emma.
但是你不懂
And you don't understand!
她才九岁
She's nine years old.
九岁的小孩怎么会杀人
Nine-year-olds don't kill people.
你到底在说什么
Listen to yourself.
你需要帮助
You need help.
让我找...
Let me come get-
她才需要帮助
She needs help,
但我不会让警察把她抓走
but I'm not gonna let them take her away.
她以后可不能在什么收容所或者
She's not gonna live the rest of her life in some institution.
监狱里度过
Or prison.
我是她父亲
I'm her father.
我必须保护她
I have to protect her.
我也尽我所能了
And I have protected her.
对不起 安琪拉
I am so sorry, Angela.
我真的很抱歉
I am so deeply sorry,
已经别无他法了
but there is no other way
我已经想好了其他的办法
and I have thought about every other option,
因为 她还会继续下去
because... she'll do it again.
大卫
David.
大卫 等等
David, wait.
你做了什么
What have you done?
都结束了
It's done.
晚安 爸爸
Night night, daddy.
你还活着
You're alive?
没错 爸爸
Yes, daddy.
我没喝你给我做的热巧克力
I didn't drink the hot chocolate you made for me.
是你喝了
You did.
我调换过了
When I switched them.
这里是警局 有什么事
911, what's your emergency?
救救我
Help me!
我爸爸要杀了我
My dad is trying to kill me!
抱歉 你能再说一遍吗
I am sorry can you say that again?
你那里是什么情况
What is your emergency?
我是艾玛·格罗斯曼 我在湖边小屋
I'm Emma Grossman and I'm at our lake house,
艾玛
Emma!
Emma?
艾玛
艾玛 我知道你在里面
Emma, I know you're in there.
艾玛 快开门
Emma! Open the door!
艾玛
Emma!
快开...
Open the-
艾玛 出来吧
Emma, just come out.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我们一起入睡
We'll just go to sleep together,
然后一起去找妈妈
and we'll go see mommy.
艾玛
Emma!
别动 大卫
Stop right there, David!
发生了什么事
What the hell's going on?
救救我
Help!
他要杀了我
He tried to kill me!
别听他胡说
Don't listen to her!
他才是罪犯
She's not right.
是他想杀了我
There's something wrong with her.
放下枪
Put down the gun.
我必须这么做
I have to do this.
走开
Leave.
我只能用这办法来保护她
I have to protect her from herself.
他们会把她抓走
They're coming for her.
我不会让你伤害她的
I will not let you hurt that girl.
问题就在这
That's just the problem.
没什么能伤到她
Nothing hurts her.
原谅我
Forgive me.
毫无疑问 他想开枪杀了那个小女孩
He was gonna shoot that little girl, no question.
我真希望我当时能早点到那里
I just wish I had gotten here sooner.
我很抱歉 艾玛
I'm so sorry, Emma.
爸爸生病了吗
Was daddy sick?
是的
Yes.
嗯 我想是的
Yes, I think so.
爸爸可能真生病了
I think your daddy was sick.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be ok.
安琪拉姑姑
Aunt Angela,
我回家后能吃冰淇淋吗
when we go home can I have ice cream?
你想要什么都行
You can have whatever you want.
本电影字幕由-=枪与惩罚=-字幕组根据电影原版字幕翻译制作
更多精彩内容请关注 枪与惩罚QQ电影群:205554694
> 片源：I Just Hope <
> 英文译本：[ 来自网络 ] <
> 字幕特效：I Just Hope <
> 后期校正：浅巷墨漓 <
> 时间轴：[来自官方译本] <
感谢观看